# Dimitrie Străoanu Web Designer | Developer





ttps://dimitriestraoanu.com

An enthusiastic, passionate and creative web designer/developer proficient with JavaScript, HTML and CSS. Quik learner, detail-oriented and a team player with excellent communication skills. I can create beautiful, responsive and user-friendly websites using only core web technologies or by using a CMS(Wordpress) for a more feature rich experience.

# Work experience:

2019

#### Web Designer/Developer

Self-employed Department: IT

2017 - 2019 | 2 ani

#### Designer

TRUSTEAM - București Department: Graphics | Industry: Advertisement

2008 - 2016 | 9 ani

## Designer

Laris Production - Focşani Department: Graphics | Industry: Advertisement

2003 - 2008 | 5 ani

## Designer

Caspro - Focșani

Department: Graphics | Industry: Advertisement

## **Education:**

2019

## Web Development

Scoala Informala de IT, București

1993 - 1997

#### High School | IT

Colegiul National Unirea, Focșani

# **Certificates:**

2019

## **Programmer Certificate**

released by National Authority for Qualifications

# **Technical skills:**

JavaScript ES6 HTML5 CSS3 **Bootstrap** Wordpress

Git/GitHub **NPM** Webpack Babel

**VS** Code **Adobe Photoshop** Adobe Illustrator **Adobe Animate Figma** CorelDraw **SolidWorks** 

# Personal skills:

**Passionate** Creative **Detail oriented Quick learner** Organized

## Languages:

**English**